(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
「なんであなたにはできないの？」
"Why is it that you can't do it?"
なんてさ
They say things like that,
陰口言われたり
being badmouthed,
呆れられたり
disappointed in,
見放されたり
and given up on.
電車は私を置き去りに
The train leaves me behind,
しちゃうし
as it always does,
葉もの野菜も腐るスピード早すぎだね
and leaf vegetables rot way too fast, don't they?
ありのままの私を好きとかだけじゃ足りないんだ
Just liking me as I am isn't enough,
愛して
love me!
毎日死ぬほど頑張ってやっと
Doing my absolute best every single day, just to barely...
ここまで連れて来られたんだ...
be able to bring myself to this point.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand,
分かってほしくもない
nor do I want you to understand.
私の苦労も
Even my struggles,
何もかも何もご存知ないでいてね
please go on knowing absolutely nothing of them.
「きっとあなたならできるはず」
"I'm sure you can do it,"
なんてさ
they say.
身の程知らずにはなりたくない
I don't want to be someone who doesn't know their place.
それでも死ぬほど頑張って
Even so, I do my absolute best,
根拠はあると思った
believing I have a reason to.
投げ出したい日もあるよ
There are days I want to throw it all away,
でも
but...
諦めたりはしない
I will never give up!
私の未来も
My future,
失敗も全部私だけのもの
and my failures are all mine alone.
あなたには分からない
You wouldn't understand,
分かってほしくもない
nor do I want you to understand.
私の苦労も
Even my struggles,
何もかも何もご存知ないでいてね
please go on knowing absolutely nothing of them.
投げ出したい日もあるよ
There are days I want to throw it all away,
でも
but...
諦めたりはしない
I will never give up!
私の未来も
My future,
失敗も全部私だけのもの
and my failures are all mine alone.
傷つかない 傷つかないでいて
Don't get hurt, don't get hurt...
可愛いだけの私でいい
Just being my cute self is enough.
三つ数えたら 素直に書いた絵
When I count to three, the drawing I drew honestly
消えてしまうけど それと同じ手
will disappear, but with those same hands...
君の顔ばかり 浮かべてたら
If I keep picturing only your face...
あ、あ、アイスみたいに とろけて
A- A- Melting like ice cream...
わかんなくなる
I lose my mind.
夢も愛も キュッとして
Holding my dreams and love tight,
いっぱいだから 持ちきれない
they're so full that I can't hold them all.
でも 欲張りすぎて
But being too greedy,
きっと 落ちていく
I'll surely fall down.
もう らっくらっくちゅっちゅ 恋に落ちちゃって
Now, Luck Luck Chu Chu, I have fallen in love,
ちゅっちゅ 戻れない
Chu Chu, I can't go back.
あれれ何で ふわりと心が
Oh my, why is my heart so light...
まだ熱くなる
...yet still getting warmer?
らっくらっくちゅっちゅ 君に夢中で
Luck Luck Chu Chu, crazy for you,
ちゅっちゅ 引き寄せて
Chu Chu, pull me close.
カレイドスコープ のぞいてるみたいで
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope.
ねえ キラキラな
Hey, a sparkling...
未来みたい 分からない
...future seems to be there, but I don't know.
さあ up and down で 手を振り回す
Now, swing your hands up and down!
秒 and 秒 今日は四六時中
Seconds and seconds, today all day long,
カレンダー 30日じゃ足りない
a 30-day calendar isn't enough.
あれもこれもそれも全部したい
I want to do this, that, and everything!
きゅん きゅきゅん 上昇 測定白書
Kyun Kyu-kyun rising, measurement white paper.
きゅん きゅきゅん 降下 深呼吸
Kyun Kyu-kyun falling, deep breath.
きゅん きゅきゅん 上昇 ラブメーター
Kyun Kyu-kyun rising, love meter.
きゅん きゅきゅん 降下 突撃GO!
Kyun Kyu-kyun falling, charge, GO!
無限大のアイ だけど失敗
Infinite AI, but a failure,
だけど諦めない
but I won't give up.
まだ 欲張りだから
Because I'm still greedy,
君と 落ちていく
I will fall down with you.
もう らっくらっくちゅっちゅ 心が回って
Now, Luck Luck Chu Chu, my heart is spinning,
ちゅっちゅ 抜け出せない
Chu Chu, I can't escape.
あれれ何で 目まぐるしい心が
Oh my, why is my dizzy heart...
まだ熱くなる
...yet still getting warmer?
らっくらっくちゅっちゅ スピード重視で
Luck Luck Chu Chu, prioritizing speed,
ちゅっちゅ 引き寄せて
Chu Chu, pull me close.
カレイドスコープ のぞいてるみたいで+
It's like looking through a kaleidoscope.
ねえ キラキラな
Hey, a sparkling...
未来みたい 分からない
...future seems to be there, but I don't know.
バーチャル リアル どっち可愛い？
Virtual, real, which one is cute?
バーチャル リアル どっちも可愛い！
Virtual, real, both are cute!
サムネ タップ はじめまして
Thumbnail tap, nice to meet you!
きゅんきゅんしたなら ハート押しといて
If your heart throbs, leave a heart.
通知はオン いつでもカモン
Notifications on, come on anytime,
一緒に踊ろうよ オン・アンド・オン
let's dance together, on and on!
お菓子食べたいけど ダイエット中
I want to eat sweets, but I'm on a diet,
君の好みに アップデート中
currently updating to your liking.
ぽちり更新 君と更新
Click and update, update with you,
もっと教えてほしいの
I want you to tell me more.
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual, real, which one do you like?
つながる1、2、3次元
Connecting the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd dimensions,
1、2、3で 飛び越えて
jump over with 1, 2, 3!
いまやネットも リアルです
Now the internet is real too,
ちくちくしないで アップデート
don't be prickly, update!
通知タップして キュンキュン
Tap the notification, kyun-kyun,
あっちもこっちも わーわー ときめきターゲット
here and there, wow wow, Tokimeki Target!
ついに達した D-One
Finally reached D-One,
待てば良いこと バーチャル リアル
good things happen if you wait, virtual real!
右に左にスワイプ ビート足して
Swipe left and right, add a beat,
きゅんきゅんしたなら 手たたいて
if your heart throbs, clap your hands.
画質低くても エンジョイしてよ
Even if the video quality is low, enjoy it,
一緒に踊ろうよ オン・アンド・オン
let's dance together, on and on!
お祝いしたいけど トラブル中
I want to celebrate, but we're having troubles,
ニュー楽しいことに サーチ中
searching for new fun things.
ぴぴぴ テレパシー 今日も配信
Pi-pi-pi telepathy, streaming today too,
もっとハートほしいの
I want more hearts.
ねえねえ どっち可愛い？
Hey hey, which one is cute?
どっち可愛い？
Which one is cute?
ねえねえ どっち可愛い？
Hey hey, which one is cute?
どっち可愛い？
Which one is cute?
どっちも可愛い！
Both are cute!
お菓子食べたいけど ダイエット中
I want to eat sweets, but I'm on a diet,
君の好みに アップデート中
currently updating to your liking.
ぽちり更新 君と更新
Click and update, update with you,
もっと教えてほしいの
I want you to tell me more.
バーチャル リアル どっちが好き？
Virtual, real, which one do you like?
バーチャル リアル どっちも好き！
Virtual, real, I like both!
つながる 1、2、3次元
Connecting 1, 2, 3 dimensions
1、2、3で飛び越えて
Fly over with 1, 2, 3!
今やネットもリアルです
Now the net is also real life
チクチクしないで ラブ&ピース
Don't prickle, love & peace
Tick Tack Tick Tack wah wah
ときめいちゃう ときかけが
My heart's throbbing, the time-leaping girl is...
つながる つながるつながるわ
Connecting, connecting, it's connecting!
待ってればいける 最強バーチャルリアル
If you wait, we can go to the ultimate virtual reality!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[On-screen: Please wait a while until the performance begins.]
僕らが見ている太陽
The sun we are looking at
って、8分前の景色で
is actually scenery from 8 minutes ago,
実はちょっと昔らしい
meaning it's technically from the past.
そう考えると不思議かもね
Thinking about it that way, it's kind of mysterious.
そこにある予定でいて
Expecting it to be there,
少しずつ違うのを過ごしてる
we spend our lives in slightly different times.
きっと僕らの交差点
Surely, at our intersection,
隣の人のことを
about the person next to us,
ひとつも知らないけれど
we don't know a single thing.
わからないままでいられなかった
But we couldn't just leave it unknown.
アマテラス この手で
Amaterasu, with this hand,
触れて 輪になって
touching and forming a circle,
踊りましょう
let's dance!
アマテラス 聴かせて
Amaterasu, let me hear you,
あのね 君だって
You know, even you
歌えるよ
can sing!
誰にだって降り注いだ
The happiness poured down on everyone,
ハッピーエンドの光が射す方へ
toward where the happy-ending light shines!
僕らは分かり合えない
We cannot fully understand each other,
お互いの世界には
in each other's worlds,
誰も価値をつけられない
no one can assign a value.
それでも隣で生きていたい
Even so, I want to live by your side,
こんなに狭い星だから
because it's such a small planet.
肩でも組んでさ 歌いましょう
Let's link shoulders and sing!
ずっと一人ぼっちはもう最後
Being all alone forever is finally over.
岩のように厚い雲を
The clouds thick as rock,
こっそり覗いた手を
the hand that peeked through secretly,
握って 掴んで
hold it, grasp it,
引っ張り出して
and pull it out!
アマテラス 光は
Amaterasu, the light,
寂しい 記憶も
even lonely memories,
同じように
in the exact same way...
アマテラス 照らしたから
Because it shone on heaven,
背中向けないで 進むだけ
don't turn your back, just move forward!
アマテラス この手で
Amaterasu, with this hand,
触れて 輪になって
踊りましょう
touching and forming a circle,
let's dance!
アマテラス 聴かせて
Amaterasu, let me hear you,
あのね 君だって
You know, even you
歌えるよ
can sing!
世界中の どんな朝も
No matter what morning in the world,
ハッピーエンドの 光に満ちている
it is filled with happy-ending light!
オキドキ 返事はいいけど
Okey-dokey, your reply is fine but
冗談なら笑えないよ
if it's a joke, it's not funny.
渋滞 曖昧 どっちを向いちゃうの
Congestion, ambiguity, which way are we facing?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
I reached my hand out to the mirage.
微熱のような 胸のものがたり
A story of the heart, like a slight fever,
そんな光は見ないフリしてさ
pretending not to see that light.
サードウェーブ 鼓動よ
Third wave, my heartbeat,
まだ行かないで まぼろしちゃ嫌だよ
don't go yet, I don't want a mirage!
私を奪って
Take me away!
魅惑のダンス ダンス ダンス
An alluring dance, dance, dance,
広がって収まらないユニバース
expanding, uncontrollable universe!
君の表情は
Your expression
私のシラバスを
my syllabus,
書き換えちゃうかも
might rewrite it
世紀末な10代で
in these apocalyptic teenage years!
Dazzling My Dream かまわず dance, dance, dance, jump and dance, dance, dance
Dazzling My Dream, don't care, just dance, dance, dance, jump and dance, dance, dance
声は闇に預けたまま
With my voice left to the darkness
目を覚ましても 離れないで
Even when I wake up, please don't leave me
Maybe maybe 正気じゃないのよ
Maybe, maybe I'm out of my mind
太陽が 忘れられない
I can't forget the sun
Darling darling そんなんじゃないから
Darling, darling, it's not like that
独り占めして Euphoria
Monopolize it, Euphoria
気にしてないような 言葉は装飾で
Words that seem unconcerned are just decoration
メイクのように 洗い流せない
They can't be washed away like makeup
360度 偽りだって
Even if 360 degrees of it are lies
かき消せるような 私にかまって
Pay attention to me, so I can drown them out
Crazy crazy love 狂わせてよ
Crazy, crazy love, drive me crazy
君の衝動は 私の深層心理を
Your impulse triggers my deepest subconsciousness
繰り返さないのよ センチメンタルね
I won't repeat it, how sentimental
過ぎ去ったネオン 三十数光年先
The past neon lights are dozens of light-years away
パノラマみたいに漂えば
If I drift like a panorama
拒む 拒む間もなかった
There was no time to even refuse
指先でまた 君を探している
With my fingertips, I'm searching for you again
その声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear your voice
私にかまって 教えてよ
Pay attention to me, tell me
恋の先の先を
What lies far beyond love
広がってくサマータイム 君の存在は
The spreading summertime, your existence...
私の脳内までも 飛び込んじゃうのよ 突き抜けてね
...jumps right into my brain, pierce through it
一世一代の dance, dance, dance, jump and dance, dance, dance
A once-in-a-lifetime dance, dance, dance, jump and dance, dance, dance
Dazzling My Dream かまわず dance, dance, dance, jump and dance, dance, dance
Dazzling My Dream, don't care, just dance, dance, dance, jump and dance, dance, dance
声は闇に預けたまま
With my voice left to the darkness
目を覚ましても 離れないで
Even when I wake up, please don't leave me
一つ、病める時も
First, in sickness,
健やかなるときも ずっと
and in health, always,
愛を 歌い続けることを
to keep singing of love,
堂々と誓います
I solemnly vow.
二つ、ボーカル、ダンスも
Second, vocal and dance,
もっと追求します
I will pursue them even more.
三つ、ずっと推してもらえる
Third, to become an idol
アイドルになってみせます
you will always support.
四つ目、不安な未来も私が照らすんだ
Fourth, even the uncertain future, I will light it up.
それでも 落ち込んじゃう日は
Even so, on days when you feel down,
思い出しているよ みんなのその笑顔
I'll be remembering all of your smiles.
未完成の地図を 輝きに変えて
Turning this incomplete map into brilliance,
誰にも真似できない 足跡を 見てて ねぇ
watching the footprints that no one else can imitate, okay?
みんなー！
Everyone!
走り出した願いは 加速していくスピード
The wishes that have started running are accelerating in speed.
目に映るものに 戸惑うなら
If you are bewildered by what you see...
仮想世界だって 私が見えてるでしょう？
Even in a virtual world, you can see me, right?
君だけにある世界が 世界
The world that exists only for you, the world...
ドキドキは 泣き出したくもなるよ
The excitement sometimes makes me want to cry,
だけどときどきが 胸を締め付ける ロマンティカ
but sometimes it tightens my chest—Romantica!
大きく手を振って 君に届けたいよ
I want to wave my hands big and reach you!
笑顔になって 未来を見に行こうよ
Let's smile and go see the future!
明けない夜だって 光のダイヤ探して
Even in an endless night, search for a diamond of light.
平気だよ 一緒に笑いたいから
It's okay, because I want to laugh together!
きれいになって ちょっぴり自信持って
Become beautiful and have a little confidence.
目から目だって ここで歌いたいの
Eye to eye, I want to sing here!
いつもより少し 大きな声で もっと
With a slightly louder voice than usual, more...
きゅんと胸を掴んで 離さないよね？
grab my heart tightly and don't let go, okay?
ねー！
Yeah!
声がちょっと小さいかも！
Your voices might be a little quiet!
スポットライトもうちょっと 当てて聞いてたい特等
Shine the spotlight a little more, I want to listen from the best seat.
不安も全部巻き込んで上がるステージで
On this rising stage, sweeping up all the anxiety...
おしとやかになって これが私のロックンロール！
Become graceful—this is my rock 'n' roll!
君だけに見せたい 私の世界
I want to show only you my world!
みんな声出していくよ！
Everyone, let me hear your voices!
せーの、ワン、ツー！
Ready, one, two!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
今日だけは一緒に 泣いてもいいよ
Today only, it's okay to cry together
だけど明日からは 明るい一歩を踏み出す準備をしててね
But from tomorrow, get ready to take a bright step forward
大きく息をして
Take a deep breath
大きく歌って 歌って 君に届けたいよ
Sing loudly, sing, I want to reach you
笑顔になって なって 未来を見に行こうよ
Smile, smile, let's go see the future
雨の日だって 風の日だって 追い風だって 向かい風だって
Whether it's a rainy day, a windy day, a tailwind, or a headwind
私たちを彩る スパイスだから
They are spices that color us
綺麗になって なって ちょっぴり自信持って
Become beautiful, beautiful, with a little confidence
デタラメだって いいよ 一緒に 歌いたいから
Nonsense is fine, because I want to sing together
いつものように 泣いて 笑って 怒って
Just like always, crying, laughing, and getting angry
歌い続けるから 魔法をかけるよ さあ
Because I'll keep singing, I'll cast a spell on you, now
せーの！もっと！もっと！
One, two! More! More!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
トイ・トイ・トイ・シュー・チュウ
Toy, Toy, Toy, Shoo-Chu
またまたトゲトゲ膨らむ
Once again getting prickly and swelling up
ぐるぐるぐるまわる脳内 倒れそうなほどに
My mind is spinning round and round, almost enough to fall over
いそがしい目で行き交うシルエット 見え隠れしたその表情
Silhouettes passing by with busy eyes, their expressions flickering in and out of sight
凍りついた街の わるい わるい 魔法に
Under the bad, bad magic of the frozen town
ゆら ゆら ゆら 退治する合図
Swaying, swaying, swaying, the signal to vanquish it
くるくる回れ エンドレスメリーゴーランド
Spin round and round, endless merry-go-round
熱くさせるこのステップ
This step that heats things up
戻れない 宇宙を スルースルーするの もっと頂戴
Passing through the universe from which there's no return, give me more
きっと届かないって分かっていてもね 揺れる心がピンチ
Even though I know it surely won't reach, my swaying heart is in a pinch
切り取ったって分かっていてもね 届かない気持ちはピンチ
Even though I know it's been cut out, these unreachable feelings are in a pinch
ひとつにしようよ ときめきしてる？
Let's make it into one, is your heart fluttering?
急がなきゃおいていかれるから ヒミツの魔法さ 準備はいい？もういいかい？
Because if we don't hurry, we'll be left behind, it's a secret magic, ready? Are you ready yet?
いない いない さあ 探して
Nowhere to be found, come on and look for me
まだまだ まだまだ 遊びましょ
Not yet, let's play some more
終わりきれない感情
Unending emotions
瞳の奥 見ててててててて
Look into the depths of my eyes
タイトな予定 期待な予定 １つずつクリアして 登場
A tight schedule, an anticipated schedule, clearing them one by one to make my entrance
どうしようかな どうしよう 暗いくらい夜も クロール クロール
What should I do, what should I do, even on a dark, dark night, crawl, crawl
大人びたお辞儀を 私の世界にようこそって
A mature bow, saying welcome to my world
手を取ってエスコートしてよ
Take my hand and escort me
きっと届かないって分かっていてもね 揺れる心がピンチ
Even though I know it surely won't reach, my swaying heart is in a pinch
切り取ったって分かっていてもね 届かない気持ちはピンチ
Even though I know it's been cut out, these unreachable feelings are in a pinch
ひとつにしようよ ときめきしてる？
Let's make it into one, is your heart fluttering?
急がなきゃおいていかれるから ヒミツの魔法さ 手と手を合わせて 踊りましょう
Because if we don't hurry, we'll be left behind, it's a secret magic, let's hold hands and dance
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
いらない真実を 忘れさせてあげるから
Because I'll make you forget the unnecessary truth
超絶の駆け引きに ちょっと溺れたら ねえ
If you drown a little in this transcendental bargaining... hey
きっと届かないって分かっていてもね 溢れる思いはプレゼント
Even though I know it surely won't reach, my overflowing thoughts are a present
切り取ったって分かっていてもね うつむく気持ちはプレゼント はじめましょう
Even though I know it's been cut out, my downcast feelings are a present, let's begin
きっと届かないって分かっていてもね 揺れる心がピンチ
Even though I know it surely won't reach, my swaying heart is in a pinch
切り取ったって分かっていてもね 届かない気持ちはピンチ
Even though I know it's been cut out, these unreachable feelings are in a pinch
ひとつにしようよ ときめきしてる？
Let's make it into one, is your heart fluttering?
急がなきゃおいていかれるから ヒミツ of 魔法さ 準備はいい？もういいかい？
Because if we don't hurry, we'll be left behind, it's a secret magic, ready? Are you ready yet?
届いたよ 君の声が さあ
Your voice reached me, now!
オフィシャル、オフィシャルにしたいけれど
Official, I want to make it official, but...
冗談だから笑えないよ
...it's a joke, so I can't laugh.
通じ合いたい どっちがどっちの
I want to connect, who is who?
真剣にもう目が回った
Seriously, my head is already spinning.
微熱の恋の物語
A story of a slightly feverish love,
そんな軽い身振りにしてた
I made such light gestures.
誘って おどけて いつまで経っても
Tease me, play around, no matter how much time passes,
そう、伏し目がちなまま
yes, with my eyes cast down.
私を奪って 魅惑 of ダンスタイム
Steal me away! A captivating dance time,
広がって止まらない 秘密のドア
expanding and unstoppable, a secret door.
駆け出しちゃったの 責任取ってよね
I've started running, so take responsibility!
さあさあ タップ タップ タップ
Now, tap, tap, tap,
タップ タップ タップ
tap, tap, tap!
声はギャップになっていくの
My voice is becoming a gap...
手をかざしても 離れないで
Even if I hold out my hands, don't leave me.
平気、平気、余裕じゃないの
Fine, fine, I'm not doing fine at all,
対応策は探せない
I can't find any way to cope.
遠い、遠い、そっちじゃないから
Far, far away, it's not over there,
振り向いてみせてよ ほらほら
turn around and show me, look, look!
気にしてないようなフリはもうよして
Stop pretending like you don't care,
迷宮のようにはぐらせない
I won't let you lose me in a labyrinth.
誘って おどけて いつまで経っても
Tease me, play around, no matter how much time passes,
そう、伏し目がちなまま
yes, with my eyes cast down.
私を奪って 狂おしくダンスタイム
Steal me away! A crazy dance time,
ハプニングが来ればチャンスでしょ？
if a happening comes, it's a chance, right?
駆け出しちゃったの 責任取ってよね
I've started running, so take responsibility!
過ぎ去ったネオンを掌に載せて
Holding the past neon lights in the palm of my hand.
涙みたいに漂えば
If I drift like a tear...
戻ることも無かった
...there was no going back.
指先で待った 君を探してるよ
Waiting at my fingertips, I'm looking for you...
その声を聞かせてよ
...let me hear that voice!
私を奪って 教えあうよ 恋のサインを
Steal me away! We'll teach each other the signs of love,
広がって止まらない 秘密のドア
expanding and unstoppable, a secret door.
私の存在は 私の将来までも
My existence, even my future,
駆け出しちゃったの 責任取ってよね
has started running, so take responsibility!
さあさあ タップ タップ タップ
Now, tap, tap, tap,
タップ タップ タップ
tap, tap, tap!
声はギャップになっていくの
My voice is becoming a gap...
手をかざしても 離れないで
Even if I hold out my hands, don't leave me.
はい！
Yes!
みなさん、新年あけましておめでとうございます！
Everyone, Happy New Year!
盛り上がってますかー？
Are you guys excited?!
みんなで協力して優しい気持ちでライブできてるかにゃ？
Are you all cooperating and enjoying the concert with a kind heart?
いいね、素晴らしいよ。
Nice, that's wonderful.
みんな見えてるよ〜！
I can see everyone!
今日はみんな青いんだね。そっか、あれか、あのTシャツ。Tシャツが...
Everyone is blue today. Oh, right, that T-shirt. The T-shirt is...
今、着てくれてる人ー？
Who is wearing it right now?
待って、当日券買ってくれた人っていますか？
Wait, is there anyone who bought same-day tickets?
おおー！ありがとうございます！
Oh! Thank you so much!
感動しちゃった、ありがとうございます。本当に嬉しいです。
I'm so moved, thank you so much. I'm really happy.
ということで、ね、やりました、あれをやりましょうか。
And so, yes, we did it. Shall we do that thing?
えー、そうですね、遠くから来てくれた人ー？
Uh, let's see. Who came from far away?
ね、飛行機とかできてくれた人いたもんね。
Right, there were people who came by plane and such.
じゃあ、海外にきにき？
How about our overseas bros?
じゃあ、声は出さなくてもいい、あのクルクルやるだけでもいいよ、女の子ー！
Then, you don't have to shout, just waving is fine... Girls!
ありがとう！前のほうでぴょんぴょん飛んでるの見えたよ。
Thank you! I saw you jumping around in the front!
奥のほうの子も見えてるよ！大声ありがとうございます！
I can see the girls in the back too! Thank you for the loud cheers!
そして、2階席！
And then, the second floor seats!
1階席！
The first floor seats!
いぇーい！
Yay!
じゃあ、またペンライト遊んじゃおう！
Let's play with the penlights again!
左の人、緑！
People on the left, green!
右の人は、じゃ、オレンジ！
And people on the right, orange!
じゃあ、真ん中は...
Then, in the middle...
青ー！
Blue!
おおー、綺麗だー！
Wow, so beautiful!
みんな、今回はね、こんな感じで、みんなも演出に参加しちゃうライブになっているよ！
Everyone, this time, it's a concert where you can all participate in the production like this!
みんなで楽しんでいこうね！
Let's all have fun together!
今日は、みんなも主役なんだ！
Today, all of you are the main characters too!
いぇーい！
Yay!
美味しい、美味しい。美味しいから、
It's delicious, delicious. Since it's delicious...
夜はね、いっぱい動くと思って。まあ、もう動いてるけど、昼から飲めばよかった。
I thought I'd move around a lot tonight—well, I'm already moving—so I should've drank it since the afternoon.
スポドリ一択！
Sports drink is the only choice!
がっつり。今年の目標みたいに、ムキムキになっていこうと思います。
Fully. I'm planning to get muscular, just like this year's goal.
がんばれ！
Do your best!
じゃあ、初めての人！
So, anyone here for the first time?
あ、着席、着席してくれてありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you for sitting down.
一番最初のライブから全部来てるよっていう人いる？
Is there anyone here who has been to every single concert since the very first one?
おー！ありがとうございます！
Oh! Thank you very much!
というわけでね、みんな分かったね？初めましての人も、いつもはそらともじゃない人も、
So, everyone, you get it now, right? Those who are here for the first time, those who aren't usually Soratomo,
そして昔から応援してる人、みんな集まって、みんなが全員そらともだよ！みんな楽しく過ごしていこうね！
and those who have supported me for a long time—everyone gathered here is a Soratomo! Let's all have a fun time together!
というわけで、なんと、YouTubeでも無料配信...
So, amazingly, we also have a free stream on YouTube...
あ、私全部言ってないのに。ふふふ。ここ、まだ来たばっかり？まだ来たばっかりかと思うけど、
Ah, I haven't said everything yet. Hehe. You guys just got here? I know you just got here, but...
続きは概要欄から、え、え、え、え、い、家（いえ）の人はどうすれば...
...the rest is from the description... wait, wait, what about the people at home?
あ、コメント会場、配信会場の人も楽しんでいってね！わーい！
Ah, those in the comment section and stream viewers, please keep enjoying it! Yay!
それでは、もう一回飲んでから行くね。ちょっと水分も大事。
Now then, I'll take one more drink before we go. Hydration is important, after all.
助かる？助かってくれてありがとう！
A lifesaver? Thanks for being saved!
では、次の曲も楽しんでいってね！
Now then, please enjoy the next song too!
まだもうちょっとだけでいいから...
Just a little bit more is fine, so...
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
[Text: The free preview stream ends here.]
The free preview ends here.